Next, let's make the skirt part, select the belt and check the specific length, and draw a circle that measures the data.
Select the outer line of the circle, select the expansion of the outer line of the plate, this expansion value is the group length, it is recommended not to make it too long, otherwise the subsequent production will be more inconvenient.
Remember to select the production inner line.
After expansion, select the inner line that has just been left, in the menu in the right-hand corner, select the conversion position.
In order to make it easier for you to arrange the plate, you can cut this half circle.
Draw two inner lines to cut this plate.
Keep one side of it, and the other side can be deleted.
Then cut along the symmetrical plate.
Arrange each with a positioning ball near the virtual model.
In order to prevent unnecessary bruising, you can freeze the sleeve version.
터
The skirt and waist are combined.
If you don't know the direction, you can use the free sewing tool to point at the 3D window during the movement, and then use the line sewing to sew the sides together.
After opening the simulation, you can see that the umbrella is complete.
Then you can expand the outline of the skirt version to lengthen the skirt.
Choose Extend from the side angle, which can extend the version along the original writing rate.
You can see that the outline of the skirt is complete.
Simulate and organize the skirt.
After that, delete the inner line and adjust the sewing line.
Add the line.
Finally, expand the outline.
You can adjust the expansion value according to your needs.
When there are more white folds,
there will be a problem of grid breakage if you expand the outside of the panel line again.
Because we have passed the ground, we need to fold it up,
otherwise there will be an unstable collision.
However, if you use a folding arrangement tool with broken panels,
the breakage will be even more serious.
So we can change a solution to close the ground collision first.
In the 3D window background, press the right button to select the model attribute,
and then close the collision under the paper surface of the attribute editor.
Open the simulation again, and the panel line can pass the ground.
Then adjust the seam line.
The panel line is now in the 3D view.
The panel line will be in the 3D view.
Now let's deal with the skirt,
so that the skirt has a collision with the ground.
First, hardening the skirt,
make the skirt become hard and hold it up.
Then apply pressure 1 to the skirt,
so that the skirt can be held up bigger.
Open the simulation,
and drag the skirt out in the process,
and drag the skirt to open the skirt.
Drag the skirt until the skirt is raised above the ground.
Then go back to the simulation attribute,
and open the collision of the ground.
Yes.
Now the result is 0 so far.
Go back to the slime tool first,
and turn the pressure down to 0
to end the hardening process.
YES.
USE the
CAN and USED у сцен to view my sculpting and the enferming process.
If it became hard after the mets,
you can try again again.
Yes.
You can also use the pressure of the small number to continue to maintain the expansion.
Click the triangle on the left side of the pressure to enter.
Test different pressure values.
If there is an obvious bulge that causes the fold to be lost, it can be appropriately reduced.
When the pressure value is 0.5, you will see that the bulge is relatively strong.
Finally, select the pressure of 0.2, which has a slight expansion effect.
Then start making the shape of the pocket body of the dress.
Select the outermost circle of the skirt, then select the inner line of the shoulder strap, and enter the value of 10 mm.
Then cut and sew them to make them an independent board.
Apply a new fabric to the edge of this circle and change the physical attribute to the leather.
The leather will turn the edge of the fabric into the curving effect of the big and thick sides.
Unlock and all of the upper parts are simulated at the same time.
For the shape of the waistline, please adjust the elastic band for it.
It will keep the original shape of the waistline.
When a strip or a piece of area is attached to the elastic band, it will continue to stay in shape.
Change the face of the shirt to a different fabric.
After the Native cotton band is sewn, the fabric is cut and pasted.
Change the fabric to a different color and temporarily use it to distinguish the different fabrics.
Because the skirt fabric pulls the upper body down, the seam allowance of the chest is not natural enough.
Use the edge seam tool to drag the seam allowance on the model to the lower position to make the curve more natural.
Do the same on the other side.
Check the other parts to see if they are stable and then freeze all the fabric.